question_data = [
    {
        "Category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The HTML5 standard was published in 2014",
        "correct_answers": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "HTML is programming language.",
        "correct_answers": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Javascript is the child of Java.",
        "correct_answers": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "CSS stands for Cascading style sheet",
        "correct_answers": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "HTML is to define the structure of web page.",
        "correct_answers": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Javascript is to add style to web page .",
        "correct_answers": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "CSS used for styling the web page",
        "correct_answers": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "We can modify tuple as list in python.",
        "correct_answers": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Dictionary is key value pair.",
        "correct_answers": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "Category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "We can build a web application in python",
        "correct_answers": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
